{
	"lessons": ["Basics", "Conversation", "Verb"],

	"Basics": [
		{
			"level": "Beginner",
			"questionSet": [
				{
					"question": "Translate \"el servicio\" to English.",
					"type": "textField",
					"answer": "the service"
				},
				{
					"question": "aproximadamente",
					"type": "radio",
					"options": ["appropriately", "possibly", "approximately", "probably"],
					"answer": "approximately"
				},
				{
					"question": "letrero",
					"type": "checkBox",
					"options": ["sign", "post", "notice", "alphabet"],
					"answer": ["sign","notice"]
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"level": "Intermediate",
			"questionSet": [
				{
					"question": "Translate \"para soportar\" to English.",
					"type": "textField",
					"answer": "to withstand"
				},
				{
					"question": "Tengo una pregunta para usted.",
					"type": "radio",
					"options": ["Ask me a question", "I have a question for you.", "Do you have any questions?", "I have an answer"],
					"answer": "I have a question for you."
				},
				{
					"question": "mañana",
					"type": "checkBox",
					"options": ["morning", "today", "tomorrow", "evening"],
					"answer": ["morning", "tomorrow"]
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"level": "Advanced",
			"questionSet": [
				{
					"question": "Translate \"los números pares\" to English.",
					"type": "textField",
					"answer": "the even numbers"
				},
				{
					"question": "salado",
					"type": "radio",
					"options": ["salad", "salty", "sugar", "sweet"],
					"answer": "salty"
				},
				{
					"question": "igualmente",
					"type": "checkBox",
					"options": ["Have a nice day", "likewise (formal)", "you too(courteous reply)", "illuminate"],
					"answer": ["likewise (formal)", "you too(courteous reply)"]
				}
			]
		}
	],

	"Conversation": [
		{
			"level": "Beginner",
			"questionSet": [
				{
					"question": "Translate \"la presidencia\" to English.",
					"type": "textField",
					"answer": "the presidency"
				},
				{
					"question": "madrastra",
					"type": "radio",
					"options": ["mother in law", "sister in law", "mother", "stepmother"],
					"answer": "stepmother"
				},
				{
					"question": "mañana",
					"type": "checkBox",
					"options": ["morning", "today", "tomorrow", "evening"],
					"answer": ["morning", "tomorrow"]
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"level": "Intermediate",
			"questionSet": [
				{
					"question": "Translate \"conocimiento intelectual\" to English.",
					"type": "textField",
					"answer": "intellectual knowledge"
				},
				{
					"question": "salado",
					"type": "radio",
					"options": ["salad", "salty", "sugar", "sweet"],
					"answer": "salty"
				},
				{
					"question": "bocadillo",
					"type": "checkBox",
					"options": ["sandwich", "tidbit", "snack", "dessert"],
					"answer":["sandwich", "tidbit", "snack"]
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"level": "Advanced",
			"questionSet": [
				{
					"question": "Translate \"el estudio\" to English.",
					"type": "textField",
					"answer": "the study"
				},
				{
					"question": "novio",
					"type": "radio",
					"options": ["uncle", "girlfriend", "boyfriend", "dad"],
					"answer": "boyfriend"
				},
				{
					"question": "cousin (choose spanish)",
					"type": "checkBox",
					"options": ["prima", "primo", "prometido", "cuñada"],
					"answer": ["prima", "primo"]
				}
			]
		}
	],

	"Verb": [
		{
			"level": "Beginner",
			"questionSet": [
				{
					"question": "Translate \"lunes\" to English.",
					"type": "textField",
					"answer": "monday"
				},
				{
					"question": "dia",
					"type": "radio",
					"options": ["light", "lamp", "day", "darling"],
					"answer": "day"
				},
				{
					"question": "yo hablo",
					"type": "checkBox",
					"options": ["I speak", "I am speaking", "please speak", "I don't speak"],
					"answer": ["I speak", "I am speaking"]
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"level": "Intermediate",
			"questionSet": [
				{
					"question": "Translate \"por ejemplo\" to English.",
					"type": "textField",
					"answer": "for example"
				},
				{
					"question": "the chair(translate to spanish)",
					"type": "radio",
					"options": ["la silla", "el sillón", "la mesa", "el basurero"],
					"answer": "la silla"
				},
				{
					"question": "yo hablo",
					"type": "checkBox",
					"options": ["I speak", "I am speaking", "please speak", "I don't speak"],
					"answer": ["I speak", "I am speaking"]
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"level": "Advanced",
			"questionSet": [
				{
					"question": "Translate \"económicamente",
					"type": "textField",
					"answer": "economically"
				},
				{
					"question": "muy aliados",
					"type": "radio",
					"options": ["very close", "seperated", "fake", "as it is"],
					"answer": "very close"
				},
				{
					"question": "ella",
					"type": "checkBox",
					"options": ["she-personal nominative pronoun","mine","her personal disjunctive pronoun","the name"],
					"answer":  ["she-personal nominative pronoun","her personal disjunctive pronoun"]
				}
			]
		}
	]

} 